Hello everyone,
welcome to the Hindi episode of Tree from German. Today
in technical terms, we are going to learn such
work which always comes with girls. So
today we are going to learn that in
episode 72, people near the doctor
asked me why this help is not invisible, this
property, so today we will see the answer to this, actually the
answer is very easy because
in Hindi or in all our Indian languages, it is
exactly the same, if you say, then
you say, answer me or I like this, if
we say, I like, then do it like this
in our languages, similarly,
when we have to say, German Mahal
Pan Helpline is a dacoit in German, this help
fruit dear shampoo, why is it, what are you doing,
you are helping, I am doing this,
if this is so, this help for dear
or
answer me, which is Mukhwas,
giving me the answer, so in unwanted
also, doubt you, all the best student and
voltage Daimler, if you did it because at what do it is like that
I like something,
I like something, no, I liked
something, I like this car,
so what should I put in this field,
understand, you saw, help, we saw, see
this file, and underworld undetected, which is
like our Hindi, this is the button, now one more
thing, as I said earlier, the
concept of polythene is saver, it does not mean that
every category of German dot is there in Hindi
also, dirty [ __ ], which is every time Bhati
in Hindi, understand the drafting concept in German also,
so I will say a little more and we see that there are
dots in German, the most
important is this dark pin, all these
for you, we do the Simran of Ji,
here I am saying thank you to someone, then
when you write this post office in the digestive system
cutter, okay, similarly your
congratulations have to be done, this
graph clear diya, this graph Twitter or the
delivery of something very important, I will give
you Islam, this Ishq love, uva, if
you want to say that this car of mine, this car
belongs to me, then we will say, we will say
Dawood  To Gy is and near Das out To Gy is
and near so till now we have seen these seven categories there are
some more such words fair learn Persian
Magre I have just given you their list which
you must be seeing you can see the base year it is
important to understand that simple concept
that why there is delay in the inside button why
postmen because give me the answer
that if one person comes to know then you just have to
remember that the
birthday team of all these words has to be put it is very simple but
accept these are the same concepts as in our Indian languages ​​you have
come here you must have understood today's conduct
we will meet in the next episode
thank you